


const trials = {
    // The practice trials to get the participant used to the experiment
    training_trials: [
        {
            question: "Bat",
            option1: 'Mammal',
            correct: 'Mammal',
            typicality: "Typical"
            
        },     
        {
            question: "Lion",
            option1: 'Mammal',
            correct: 'Mammal',
            typicality: "Typical"
            
            
        },
        {
            question: "Rabbit",
            option1: 'Mammal',
            correct: 'Mammal',
            typicality: "Typical"
            
        }  
    ],
    // In these trials we collect the relevant data
    main_trials: [
        {
            question: "Frog",
            option1: 'Amphibian',
            option2: 'Reptile',
            correct: 'Amphibian',
            typicality: "Atypical"
            
        },
        {
            question: "Dolphin",
            option1: 'Mammal',
            option2: 'Fish',
            correct: 'Mammal',
            typicality: "Atypical"
            
        },
        {
            question: "Seal",
            option1: 'Mammal',
            option2: 'Fish',
            correct: 'Mammal',
            typicality: "Atypical"
            
        },
        {
            question: "Seaturtle",
            option1: 'Amphibian',
            option2: 'Fish',
            correct: 'Amphibian',
            typicality: "Atypical"
            
        },
        {
            question: "Salamander",
            option1: 'Reptile',
            option2: 'Amphibian',
            correct: 'Reptile',
            typicality: "Atypical"
            
        },
        {
            question: "Seahorse",
            option1: 'Fish',
            option2: 'Mammal',
            correct: 'Fish',
            typicality: "Atypical"
            
        },
        {
            question: "Dove",
            option1: 'Bird',
            correct: 'Bird',
            typicality: "Typical"
            
        },
        {
            question: "Cow",
            option1: 'Mammal',
            correct: 'Mammal',
            typicality: "Typical"
            
        },
        {
            question: "Eagle",
            option1: 'Bird',
            correct: 'Bird',
            typicality: "Typical"
            
        },
        {
            question: "Tuna",
            option1: 'Fish',
            correct: 'Fish',
            typicality: "Typical"
            
        },
        {
            question: "Fly",
            option1: 'Insect',
            correct: 'Insect',
            typicality: "Typical"
            
        },
        {
            question: "Cangaroo",
            option1: 'Mammal',
            correct: 'Mammal',
            typicality: "Typical"
            
        },
        {
            question: "Ant",
            option1: 'Insect',
            correct: 'Insect',
            typicality: "Typical"
            
        },
        {
            question: "Guineapig",
            option1: 'Mammal',
            correct: 'Mammal',
            typicality: "Typical"
            
        },
        {
            question: "Mosquito",
            option1: 'Insect',
            correct: 'Insect',
            typicality: "Typical"
            
        },
        {
            question: "Zebra",
            option1: 'Mammal',
            correct: 'Mammal',
            typicality: "Typical"
            
        },
        {
            question: "Clownfish",
            option1: 'Fish',
            correct: 'Fish',
            typicality: "Typical"
            
        },
        {
            question: "Elephant",
            option1: 'Mammal',
            correct: 'Mammal',
            typicality: "Typical"
            
        },
        {
            question: "Snake",
            option1: 'Reptile',
            correct: 'Reptile',
            typicality: "Typical"
            
        }, 
    ],
    // These trials are an expansion of the original experiment
    // We want to test, if the same effect also appears in other domains 
    exploration_trials: [
        {
            question: "Berlin",
            option1: 'Non-Capital',
            option2: "Capital",
            correct: 'Capital',
            typicality: "Typical"
            
        }, 
        {
            question: "London",
            option1: 'Non-Capital',
            option2: "Capital",
            correct: 'Capital',
            typicality: "Typical"
            
        }, 
        {
            question: "Paris",
            option1: 'Non-Capital',
            option2: "Capital",
            correct: 'Capital',
            typicality: "Typical"
            
        }, 
        {
            question: "Rom",
            option1: 'Non-Capital',
            option2: "Capital",
            correct: 'Capital',
            typicality: "Typical"
            
        }, 
        {
            question: "Moscow",
            option1: 'Non-Capital',
            option2: "Capital",
            correct: 'Capital',
            typicality: "Typical"
            
        },  
        {
            question: "Barcelona",
            option1: 'Non-Capital',
            option2: "Capital",
            correct: 'Non-Capital',
            typicality: "Atypical"
            
        },  
        {
            question: "Sydney",
            option1: 'Non-Capital',
            option2: "Capital",
            correct: 'Non-Capital',
            typicality: "Atypical"
            
        },  
        {
            question: "Beijing",
            option1: 'Non-Capital',
            option2: "Capital",
            correct: 'Capital',
            typicality: "Atypical"
            
        },  
        {
            question: "Ottawa",
            option1: 'Non-Capital',
            option2: "Capital",
            correct: 'Capital',
            typicality: "Atypical"
            
        },  
        {
            question: "Saigon",
            option1: 'Non-Capital',
            option2: "Capital",
            correct: 'Non-Capital',
            typicality: "Atypical"
            
        },  
        {
            question: "Dubrovnik",
            option1: 'Non-Capital',
            option2: "Capital",
            correct: 'Non-Capital',
            typicality: "Atypical"
            
        },  
        {
            question: "Salzburg",
            option1: 'Non-Capital',
            option2: "Capital",
            correct: 'Non-Capital',
            typicality: "Typical"
            
        },  
        {
            question: "Las Vegas",
            option1: 'Non-Capital',
            option2: "Capital",
            correct: 'Non-Capital',
            typicality: "Typical"
            
        },  
        {
            question: "Rio de Janeiro",
            option1: 'Non-Capital',
            option2: "Capital",
            correct: 'Non-Capital',
            typicality: "Atypical"
            
        },     
    ]
};
        